Get in the house.
Hey, hey, hey.
How many bloody
times do we have to do this?
It's not my fault.
It's his fault.
- I'll take care of him.
- Michael, can you hear me?
It's fine.
Why are
you protecting him?
I thought you'd grown up by now.
Can you hear me?
Don't you touch him!
Why
don't you listen to me, Michael?
I can do what I like.
He's my son.
Leave him alone!
Listen!
Freak.
I'm the only one who can freak
him, ain't I, Michael?
Why ain't you listening to me?
You're not gonna do
that...not that...
Why aren't you
listening to me?
Stop!
You're not gonna
embarrass me anymore.
You bully! Get
out! Get out! Get out! Get out!
Hello?
Right now? I'm late for work.
Can I come in later?
Okay.
Okay. I'll be there.
Shit.
I can't believe I'm
hearing this. Are you serious?
Is she serious?
This is a joke,
an absolute joke.
I think the key issue
here is accountability.
- Accountability?
- Your brother
is in clear breach
of our code of conduct.
We have no choice but
to terminate
his placement
here immediately.
That's good. That's really good.
I appreciate
that you're upset.
Excuse me?
- Do you need to get that?
- No.
- Let's just calm down.
- Calm down?
- Don't tell her to calm down.
- I am wary of his triggers.
I'm purely looking out
for Michael.
No, you're not.
This is, what, the seventh,
no, eighth placement
to have fallen through.
Ninth. It's the ninth placement.
Right. See? Ninth.
There was Rose House,
Clinton House, Thomas Lodge.
- Yes, ninth.
- Inckenfield Lane.
Rose House again, counts as
twice. Ford Lands, Goldsmiths...
- Yes. Thanks, Michael.
- Lantern and here.
- That makes nine.
- Thank you.
You're welcome.
Someone stole confidential
care home account information
and leaked it
to the local press.
Someone. You don't know that
was Michael. Where's the proof?
It's not the first
time your brother
has bypassed our
online security.
It could have been anyone.
And, actually, if you
hadn't been stealing from people
you're supposed
to be looking after,
maybe there'd be
nothing for anyone to leak.
Technically,
it is a criminal matter.
Your brother's lucky we're not
pressing charges for data theft.
Theft? You stole money from him
and now you're kicking him out.
Well, it sounds like Michael
would be better off
living with you.
A hundred percent.
I'm sorry. We have no choice.
His placement here
is no longer tenable.
Michael needs to leave.
Today. Now.
Great.
I have work. I don't even
have time to get your things.
We'll forward them on.
Fuck.
You'll be
hearing from my lawyer.
- Like you have a lawyer.
- She doesn't know that.
Derek, I was just about to call.
Late and full of shit.
We've spoken about this, Joey.
Technically,
I'm not that late.
Technically, you're sacked.
No, no, no, no. Look, Derek,
it was a family emergency.
Please, I cannot lose this job.
I swear I'll be there by...
Two. Get here by two.
So, how was your day?
Well, first my boss
was being a...
Please don't swear.
Bad word. Cos I was late.
Then I got a call
to come and get you.
And cos my boss is a bad word,
if I'm not in by two,
the bad word will sack me.
Apart from that, great. You?
Yeah, I'm happy.
I get to be with my sister.
Oh, please don't swear.
- For fuck...
You wouldn't know who hacked the
care home account to leak them?
- Are you cross? You seem cross.
- Yeah, I am.
With the care home,
and those wankers
- for stealingy our allowance.
- Joanna.
- They have to face justice.
- They do.
Just not sure they will.
It's not how the world works.
That's why I wanna be
a crusader for the truth.
Like Piers Morgan.
Piers Morgan is an
attention-seeking
the worst word.
Well, Piers Morgan wouldn't
have got on the wrong bus.
Fuck!
No more swearing.
I said I'm sorry.
Motherf...
Stop. Stop! Stop, stop, stop!
- My charger. I left my charger.
- We'll get one later.
- You don't understand.
- Michael...
I'm at seven fucking percent!
Where is my fucking charger?
- No! No!
- Michael. Michael.
- You...
- Michael.
- You don't... You...
Do you need a squeeze?
- I'm so sorry.
- I know.
- I'm sorry.
- I'm sorry too.
When are we going home?
You'll have to hang
here till I finish at six.
Six? That's two Lord
of the Rings.
Or one extended edition.
I've got five minutes.
Come on.
Big Ron will keep an eye on you.
He'll make sure you're okay.
How's it going, Michael?
Does he know I'm autistic?
He knows. He's cool.
It'll be fine.
Does he have a charger?
I can sort that
out for you, mate.
And he'll look after your bag.
I'll be back in a minute.
There's a lot of people.
It's busy.
There's a party tonight.
We're not invited and
you hate parties.
Can't I just come with you?
You could get me a job here.
You don't wanna work here.
My bosses are dicks.
- Well, you do.
- Outside the building.
Away from the dicks.
I'll be back.
And home...
Am I staying with you?
- Until we find a new placement.
- I don't like the placements.
We'll talk about this later.
I have to go.
- It's always later.
- You're staying tonight.
For how long?
I need to go.
Stay with Big Ron.
Sorry, sorry, sorry.
The gala is all set.
18:00 hours,
guests arrive, cocktails begin.
18:20, Geoffrey to give
brief shareholder speech.
I've allowed 30 minutes.
18:21, my will to live expires.
Oh, and just to flag,
there will be live performers
before and after.
It's gonna be all Cirque du
Soleil crap, isn't it?
Just make sure they
give us a wide berth.
I want a fucking
ten-metre exclusion zone.
- The theme's divine renewal.
- I really don't give a shit.
Are you dipping, Gerald?
Yes. I think
I'm fucking dipping.
Jesus Christ. Breathe in.
You'd better not fucking
drop now. You should be at home.
Maybe if you paid proper
maternity leave, she would be.
17 seconds. I made it.
We really need to have a chat
about your attitude, Joey.
It's no wonder
the army kicked you out.
Love to. Got to get to work.
My boss can be a real
pain in the arse.
Your boss would love you to.
You still owe me an hour,
at least.
- What?
- I'll add it on.
You can start with a...
bird strike.
- Come on.
- Level 51, panel F 51 P 118.
Should be
properly baked on by now.
- That's borderline harassment.
- Enjoy. Enjoy. Enjoy.
Ooh!
- Missed a bit.
- Definitely not funny.
See, I thought you weren't
even coming in today, slacker.
- Some of us are almost done.
- I had to sort something.
Oh, yeah?
They kicked Michael
out of his care home.
- Oh, man. What?
- Yeah.
He hacked their records, accused
them of stealing his money.
- So, yeah, it's a shitshow.
- Fuck.
That's my El Capitan
climb screwed.
Shit, I'm so sorry,
man. How's he doing?
- He's alright.
- Oh, yeah?
- He's downstairs.
- You brought him here?
It was that or get fired.
It's cool. He's with Big Ron.
Alright, Michael? Have that.
Is my phone charged?
Hold on.
Oi!
- Gerald?
- That cleaner in the lift.
There were two
cleaners in the lift.
The non-pregnant one.
- The lippy one.
The window cleaner.
We can't sack her
for being lippy
if that's what
you're about to ask.
- I'll call her line manager.
- Do it.
Nice of you to join us.
- Bloody hate these things.
- Yes.
Well, if you could possibly find
it within yourself
to soldier through.
- Fine.
- And smile.
Good to see you.
Gerald. You're looking well.
- Am I? Shall we do this?
- Yes.
Right, I'll tee up,
you play off.
Nothing too taxing, I promise.
- Great.
- Absolutely.
With me are
Geoffrey and Gerald Milton,
owners and CEOs
of Agnian Energy.
Thank you for joining me.
- Pleasure.
- Absolutely.
Demand has never been higher,
but there is
a great deal of uncertainty
in the energy markets right now.
Agnian is riding high.
You have your shareholder
gala this evening to celebrate.
What is Agnian doing right?
Here at Agnian, we see
meeting the world's energy needs
as a privilege and a duty.
Absolutely.
Billions of people
depend on energy,
but it has to be provided
sustainably and responsibly.
Absolutely.
My brother and I
and everyone here at Agnian
are passionate about cleaner
strategies for a cleaner future.
Absolutely.
Want some?
Ooh!
- Nice.
- Oh, shit.
There's a bird strike on 51.
Derek wants you to clean it.
Right. And he just
forgot to tell me.
- Okay.
- He did.
- Sure.
- So I'm telling you now.
- Stop it.
- 51.
Stop it.
You're embarrassing yourself.
- Who got you this job?
- Not so I could do yours.
Fuck it. I'll get to it later.
Agnian
believes in reducing emissions,
not output.
We believe in action,
not pledges.
Our commitment to renewable
energy is not just a promise,
it's a path we walk every day.
So what do you think?
I'm thinking, 'Jesus Christ.
How much did that cost?'
Thank you, ladies and gentlemen.
You're very kind,
but you haven't heard...
I'll get that fixed.
No, well,
don't feel you have to.
And we want you to join us
in our shared journey towards
a brighter, cleaner future.
Now who's slacking?
You gotta enjoy
these moments, Joey.
Human life is a fleeting thing.
- All flesh is grass.
- Thanks, Buddha.
Look at us,
just like fuckin' ants, just...
Hey, do you ever wonder what
it was like before we were here?
Are you high?
- Hey, Noah.
- Hey, Derek.
You need to finish up.
The gala starts in an hour.
Okay. Wow.
- We have to clear the building.
- No, listen,
I don't know how you
make it through the day, mate.
You're an inspiration
to all of us, D, genuinely.
Yeah, I've been told
to wrap it up.
- Yeah, okay.
- You need to finish up.
Derek says turn
your earpiece on.
He knows it's not broken.
- He's smart like that.
- Hi, Derek.
You pissed off
a Milton in the lift.
He was being a dick.
When you own the building,
you get to be a dick.
- What's your excuse, D?
- Clean the fucking bird.
Right, I'm done.
Have a good one, yeah?
Listen, I hope it's all
okay with Michael, seriously.
Look after him, yeah? I mean,
I know you know that, but...
Maybe take him somewhere
nice after you knock off.
- Will do, Dad.
- Later, Joey.
Right.
This is an important night.
These are important people.
Let's make sure it's a good one.
Clear as you go,
drinks topped up...
It's our values.
Agnian Values.
Sustainability.
- Hi, Joey.
- You can't be up here, Michael.
You'll get me sacked.
Go down. I'll be two minutes.
- I want to go home.
- Get in the lift and go down.
- You can't tell me what to do.
- Yes, I can. Go down.
- Fuck off!
- I don't need this shit.
- Fuck you, Joanna!
- No! Fuck you!
Go on, then!
Where are you going? Come back!
- Away from you, like you want!
- Fuck!
Shit.
Have you cleaned that bird yet?
- It's done. I'm coming up.
- Nah ah ah ah.
Nice try. Get in.
I'll take you there.
Or you're not clocking off.
Derek, I've got
something I have...
Bullshit.
Get on with it.
Fuck.
Fuck!
Prick.
Prick
with his finger on the override.
But it's our values,
it's Agnian values...
- Geoffrey.
- Erica.
So my video's
going down a storm.
Oscar worthy.
I want much more than that.
Really?
Say, VP of brand strategy?
No doubt you're to blame
for inflicting the
Shit de Soleil on us.
'Du.' It's 'du Soleil',
Geoffrey.
'Du' you think I care?
Where the hell is Gerald?
Oh. Last seen
dry-humping Alison Pope.
Alison Pope? From Morgan?
And don't erupt, but the
performers are going to be late.
Alison-fucking-Pope. Jesus.
Fuck you, Derek.
Fuck.
Are you okay?
What was that?
Okay, done. Get me up, Derek.
Derek? Derek!
Just going for a slash.
Back in five.
Maybe ten.
Just get me up.
Where the fuck have you been?
And don't say traffic.
We've all got GPS.
Geoffrey's about to go on,
so you'll have to wait.
I'd get in there and show face.
Cheers.
Excuse me.
Idiot.
Good evening.
Thank you, ladies and gentlemen.
You're very kind.
But you haven't heard
what I have to say yet.
And we are not going to.
Come on.
But what a year,
and if I have to tell you just
how good it's been,
I suggest you
hire new accountants.
Come on, Derek, Jesus.
You know what
your problem is, Joey?
Is it the prick with
his finger on the override?
It was a joke, Derek.
What are you doing?
Derek!
You did not have
to fucking kill them.
Stick to the plan.
Derek, stop dicking around.
And we are in.
Because it's our values,
Agnian values...
Yes, we do have them.
Sustainability, transparency,
responsibility, trust,
which drive our mission.
Beautiful.
Beautiful words, Geoffrey.
Very inspiring.
If only a single
one of them was true.
Four hours till
the fairy dust wears off.
Bibbidy-bobbidy bye-bye!
We are Earth Revolution,
and our takeover tonight
will usher in a new dawn.
If you are good,
if you play nice,
I promise you
will live to see it.
Ooh, sounds so scary.
Lifts and doors
locked up to your level.
All calls and comms jammed.
No alarms raised.
This is our house now.
Greedy, Needy, Sleazy,
Selfish,
Snorty, Deceitful, Cocky.
We're one short. Where's Gropey?
Geoffrey, where's Gerald?
Where's your brother, G?
I only ask once.
527!
Apartment 527.
There we go.
Wakey, wakey, hands off snakey.
Hey, Gerry.
Let's go.
Ooh. Steady, now.
Window cleaner. Window cleaner.
What's that, Gerry?
Window cleaner.
And there was me thinking that
you never gave us a second look.
What the fuck?
Who owns
the building now, Gerry?
Help! Help! Hey!
Look up! Hey!
Look up! Hey! Hey...
...up!
Shit.
Okay, Joey,
get a grip. Michael needs you.
Stay calm,
Michael. Joanna needs us.
Think, think, think.
What would...what would
Piers Morgan do?
Room service.
Where d'you want him?
We're on the clock. Let's go.
Make him decent.
Noah.
Marcus Blake. Cheers.
Mmm!
Duval-Leroy. Very nice.
Let's have no hysterics,
no heroics, no drama.
You think this is the
first time people
have tried to take
money from us?
Let us go, and whatever you
were hoping to steal,
we'll double it.
He thinks we want their money.
We don't want your money, Geoff.
- What do you want?
- We wanna save the world.
I don't understand.
I love this
'Friends of the Earth' stuff.
'Fuel your life the green way.'
Jesus Christ. Zee?
Agnian
believes in reducing emissions,
not output.
We believe in action,
not pledges.
Our commitment to renewable
energy is not just a promise,
it's a path we walk every day.
And we want you to join us
in our shared
journey towards a brighter...
Doesn't look like
friendship to me, Geoffrey boy.
It doesn't, does it?
I mean, do friends plunder,
choke and rape?
Noah, we can't do this
without them. Let him go.
I said let him go!
You'll have to forgive him.
He gets a little excited.
Right, so this
is Laguna Taracoa.
You should know it
because Agnian has been dumping
billions
of gallons of waste there,
an entire ecosystem
completely destroyed.
Ring any bells?
No? How about now?
Elena Lanza. She was with us
when we sabotaged
the Taracoa
pipeline last year.
She was caught
and was gonna use the trial
to tell the world what
you've been doing there.
No?
How about this?
You had her killed.
Elena was found
murdered in her cell,
so the trial never
takes place.
No smoke without fire,
right? So what do you do?
You sit down with your
friends in Parliament,
the press,
social media,
you downplay, deny,
keep the disinformation pumping,
just so long as those
oil licences keep coming
and the Agnian
stock keeps climbing.
Zee.
There's a Taracoa every
month and Elena every week.
And the world does nothing.
Until now.
Tonight you are accountable.
You can't prove any of this.
You're right,
Geoffrey, we can't, but you can.
You fucking cowards.
You won't get away with it.
Did you say 'cowards'?
We've stood before
bulldozers in the Amazon,
been shot at by whalers,
seen our brothers and sisters
killed for what they believe in.
What are you?
You're a fat,
ugly man in a suit.
Are you insane?
Are you hearing this?
So this is what's gonna happen.
You are gonna
give Zee your passwords
and she's gonna expunge
every guilty secret
from your accounts.
You're then gonna
confess your crimes.
We're gonna shine a
light on every lie,
bribe and abuse
and then reveal it to the world.
Once the truth goes viral,
you and Agnian stock
will be worthless.
Provided you comply,
you will then be released.
By us at least.
What happens beyond that,
out of my hands.
Let's discuss this.
We have everyone here to
give you a platform.
You don't understand,
Geoffrey. You are the platform.
But you said yourself,
you need people onside.
Come on.
We can talk this through.
What the hell
is wrong with you?
Enough fucking talk.
Marcus, you're breaking bread
with them and having a go at me?
- Fuck you.
- We agreed, no killing.
You knew exactly who I
was before you brought me.
Noah, this is not the way.
All flesh is grass, man.
Oh, enough of your
fucking bullshit.
Without me, you
wouldn't have even got in here.
You'd still be on
the outside throwing rocks.
So wind your fucking neck in and
remember what we're here to do.
We've got multiple reports
of an SOS at Agnian Tower.
Someone's lit a signal
halfway up the building.
What the fuck is this?
Just
a little extra persuasion.
I hate to interrupt
circle time,
but we have an iceberg on
the horizon.
- Police inbound rapid response.
- How?
There's a fucking SOS
on the side of the building.
- Someone went old school.
- Outside?
What, one of the cleaners?
Find them.
Zee, send
a message to the police
warning we have hostages.
No.
Noah, we have a runner.
The cleaner's
not going anywhere. Get Gerald.
Zee, there's
an override to the cradle.
Sweet.
Bring her up. Bring her in.
That was very,
very stupid, Gerald.
Window cleaner banjaxed
the cradle. She's stuck.
- One down from you.
- Fuck her.
Let her sweat.
You've already killed one
Milton. We can't lose 'em both.
Nobody's listening to you,
Marcus.
What is this, a fucking coup?
- Put the gun down.
- You know,
I don't think I will.
You wanna pull this
shit when we're this close?
But we're not close,
are we? We're not fucking close.
You stupid, arrogant bastard.
Nothing has changed,
bro. The world is still dying.
Fuck this hearts and
minds bullshit.
It's time for some
shock and awe.
Noah, put the fucking
gun down or I'll put you down.
No, you won't.
That's why I have to do this.
See, you, you're lucky,
Gerry. You, I need.
But I'm in now, Marcus,
and I'm gonna be throwing
a lot more than fucking rocks.
I'm only gonna ask you this
once, Wyatt. Are you in or out?
Zee?
Looks like I'm all in.
Look, I'm sorry,
man. Really, I am.
But you still think
that people are the solution.
People are the problem.
I mean, look at me.
It's too late for a revolution,
Marcus. This is a reckoning.
Zee, stream this to our guests.
So, Gerry's had his fun, and
after a brief chat with Marcus,
the headline is we're
now under new management.
I know some of you were loyal
to Marcus, but that's done.
It's my way now. Same broad
strokes, just a few key changes.
True believers only.
Every movement
needs its martyrs.
Who's on the outside now?
Try running now.
As soon as we're done, you
get the explosives ready, okay?
What about your cleaner?
We should get rid of her.
And we've a chopper inbound.
Helicopter in the air.
That's full pig bingo.
Please tell me this shitshow
comes with a fucking plan.
Relax, Zee. They're
still coming clean tonight.
You're still gonna dig
through all their dirty laundry.
Marcus was right about one
thing. The truth does matter.
Without it, they'll just
smear us as cranks and crazies,
a bunch of murdering psychos,
but the truth by itself
changes nothing.
Strap 'em up.
You've got this,
Joey, like riding a bike,
700 feet high in
a mangled fucking cradle
having dead bodies
thrown at you.
I really wish you
weren't here right now.
Derek had to be Derek.
Course he did.
Now, are you gonna try
and talk me out of it too, Joey?
Like he did? No.
Okay.
You're killing people, Noah.
I am killing people,
the ones that get in my way.
But it's not personal.
Actually, you know what?
Fuck that.
It is kind of deeply personal.
But everyone's got a personal,
Joey. What's yours?
And Michael?
Please tell me
he's not still here.
He left. Got bored waiting.
Hey, guys, our cleaner's
little brother, Michael Locke,
is somewhere in the building.
Zee'll send you
a picture of him now.
Could you find him
and bring him to me?
Poor fucking bastard.
You leave him stuck in
some shithole home for years.
You talk about him
like he's an embarrassment.
Like somehow you've
had it tougher than him.
- That's not true.
- Yes, it is fucking true.
Don't lie to yourself
right now, Joey.
And then the one time
that you are here for him,
you bring him into this.
Sister of the fucking year,
you are.
If you touch him...
- I thought he'd left.
- I will end you.
Oooh. That's a bit dark,
isn't it?
I told you. Personal.
My name is Denise Slater.
I am the minister for energy.
I speak to you
today to confess to actions
- that I can no longer conceal.
- Fuck. Come on.
For years, I have
accepted bribes from Agnian.
I received in
excess of £2 million
to obstruct
an inquiry into Agnian's site...
Sierra Oscar.
Units on route
to the Agnian Tower.
We're way off on the hack.
They've only just
started spilling their guts.
And we've got maybe two
minutes till the feds show.
Noah, we're not ready.
We need more time.
Your guests are almost here.
You invited them,
Joey. This is your night.
999.
There's a crazy woman outside
the Agnian Tower with a gun.
She's gonna kill someone. You
need to get here. Get here now.
You fucking psycho.
- I thought we were friends.
Well, friends help each other,
don't they?
So why don't you
point that gun at the street,
straight down,
and empty the clip?
Go fuck yourself.
Oh, shit.
Look who it is.
Halina.
- She's nothing to do with them.
- She takes their money. Shoot.
- Noah, she's pregnant.
- Even more of a reason.
This is no world to be bringing
a kid into, now, is it?
Don't do it, please.
If you don't want her to die,
all you have to do is
get shooting.
Lose the silencer.
Let's make a bang.
And no easy shots.
Make 'em dance.
See? I told you.
Like fucking ants.
Okay, got the target.
Let's go! Everybody! Now!
Out! Come on!
Come on! Quickly, move!
- Out, out! Go, go, go! Come on!
- This way.
Out now!
You're sick!
I'll let you know
when we find Mikey.
Turn around.
Put your hands in the air.
We're hearing reports that
the Agnian Tower is under siege.
While we are awaiting
confirmation of hostages,
we can confirm that
several shots
were fired from halfway up
the building itself
by an as yet unidentified woman.
I think it's fair to
say the cleaner
has their full attention.
Well,
let's make sure she keeps it.
Transfer some
of the Milton brothers' funds
into Joanna Locke's account.
Say, 33 million.
I'm sorry. How many million?
- Guv.
- Yes.
Ground commander for the night.
Lucky you, right?
Yeah, lucky me.
Right, what we got?
Nothing on the hostages yet.
Shareholder event for Agnian.
We have workers,
staff and high-profile guests,
including Denise Slater,
the minister for energy.
We have 102 phone signals,
all non-responsive.
No demands as yet,
but the SOS was followed
by a coded
warning about the hostages,
then the call
about the shooter.
Casualties?
One body on the cradle with
the shooter. None on the ground.
Spotters have ID'd
the shooter as Joanna Locke,
one of the window cleaners.
Ex-army. SRR.
Made it through
Marine selection,
only to assault a squad mate,
then quit.
Troubled childhood,
abusive father, brother in care.
Drug fines, self-medicating.
- Classic unstable ex-soldier.
- Yeah, maybe.
Get urgent authorities in place
for her socials,
her phones, her finances.
You know, a deep,
detailed picture,
not a way too easy, lazy answer.
Yes, guv. Sorry, guv.
No, you could be right.
Let's see.
We're gonna have to ruin
the commissioner's bridge night.
He'll need to brief the home
secretary and the mayor.
Who have we got from SCO19?
- Stormin' Norman.
- Yeah, course. Who else?
Right, well, if I get too
punchy, just give me the signal.
Yes, guv.
What do I do when you ignore it?
Speak of the devil.
- Snipers are in place, ma'am.
- Thank you.
Yes, we need to make
contact with the shooter,
work out what
the hell is going on.
- Waiting for your mark.
- Yes, I heard. Thank you.
I've got the shot.
I'm not with them!
Don't shoot! Don't shoot!
I'm not one for doing nothing.
We're not doing nothing, Royce.
We're waiting
till we learn more.
If she lit that sign
because she wanted attention,
she's not putting on
much of a show,
no matter how much someone
wants us to think that.
Nobody makes
a move unless I say so.
- Ma'am.
- Hmm?
Thirty-three million just landed
in Joanna Locke's account.
From the Milton brothers.
She's just fired seven rounds
into St. Thomas's Street.
Into the street.
Now, either that's blind luck
or she's ex-SRR,
she knows exactly how
to hit a target and miss one.
Unless she's unstable.
She's going
for the body.
Hold your fire.
She's holding a device.
999. What's
your emergency?
Are you fucking kidding me?
Guv. For you. It's Joey Locke.
Tell the chopper to back off.
Hello, Joey?
Don't shoot!
I'm not with them.
We won't shoot.
This is
Superintendent Claire Hume.
And I repeat,
we will not shoot.
Great.
We're gonna get you
down as soon as we can.
Forget about me.
You need to get inside.
- And we will.
- My brother's in the building.
- His name is Michael Locke.
- We're gonna get him too.
You have to find him,
please. Please.
You mentioned a 'them'?
My news outlets,
under my personal direction,
have consistently,
repeatedly, perpetuated the myth
- that climate change is a hoax.
- Naughty boy.
It's time to admit my complicity
in the downplaying
of climate change.
I didn't do anything.
I shouldn't be here.
Hey, hey, hey. Don't
undersell yourself, Jennifer.
You know where all
the bodies are buried.
Now, you can either
tell us where to dig,
or you can join Geoff here.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Is he freaking you out?
Do you want me to move him?
No.
Someone needs to get inside.
Oh, believe me, we're on it.
We just need to assess.
Hume, listen to me...
Joey, I'm gonna have to call you
back, but we will get you down.
I don't wanna get down.
I wanna get in.
Fuck!
Noah Santos.
No socials and no record.
Clean as a whistle.
I cross-checked his work ID.
They match with this guy.
He was calling
himself Lucas Vander then,
a member of the Seventh Harvest,
an anti-humanist group.
- Anti-humanist? As in...?
- As in...
Man is a blight upon the world.
A cancer, a virus.
And for the human
virus to be controlled
requires a radical,
invasive approach.
Delightful.
Close to no followers.
On the fringes of the fringe.
Not even worth
putting on the watch list.
But last year
he shows up in the orbit
of someone who
was on the watch list.
Marcus Blake.
The man we just
peeled off the pavement.
Leader of Earth Revolution,
a radical environmental group.
Extreme but organised.
Well connected, well resourced.
Linked to the sabotage
of the Dakar refinery
and the Laguna Taracoa
facility last year.
Laguna Taracoa? That's Agnian.
There were warnings given
at those attacks. No casualties.
One was arrested at Taracoa,
practically handed herself in.
It's the Earth Revolution MO.
Get attention, make their case.
Only this time, Elena Lanza
gets herself knifed
in jail for the cause.
So, Marcus Blake,
an extremist, not a killer.
Now he's dead,
murdered by Noah Santos.
Dial me in.
Do it.
The first casualty
at the Agnian siege in London
has been
identified as environmentalist
and radical
eco-activist Marcus Blake.
With Blake dead, it is
not yet clear
who is in control of what is a
rapidly escalating situation.
Through no choice of my own,
I, James Horsley,
am compelled to reveal the truth
about my part in regards to
Agnian and the Milton brothers.
I personally oversaw the payment
of millions in settlements
to silence whistleblowers
and complainants.
All people are like grass
and all their faithfulness
like the flowers in the field.
Grass withers
and the flowers fall,
but the breath
of the Lord remains forever.
- You good?
- I'm terrified.
What happens if
it loses my pulse?
You'll have about five seconds
for it to find it again.
Good to know.
Superintendent Claire Hume
is on the line.
Hmm, patch her through.
Are you still with
us for phase two, Zee?
Yes.
Great to have you onboard.
- Noah Santos?
- Detective Claire Hume.
Superintendent. But,
then, I think you knew that.
Would you prefer Noah or Lucas?
Let's stick with Noah.
I outgrew Lucas.
Are you in charge
down there, Claire?
Yes. You in charge up there?
I am now, yeah.
What happened
with Marcus Blake?
Creative differences.
Your boys in the chopper
and on the rooftops should know
that I'm wearing a dead man's
switch synched to my pulse,
so if my heart stops beating,
the whole building explodes.
Likewise,
any attempt to gain access,
cutting the power,
and I start detonating hostages.
If you think I might blink,
ask Marcus Blake.
As the CEO of Beacon Social...
Gerald
and the board are confessing
to their systemic
violation of the planet.
They're far from
the only guilty ones.
You're putting
them on trial.
Tonight's about consequences,
Claire. You reap what you sow.
Okay, well, while
they're confessing,
why don't we let the others go?
I understand you have
issues with the Miltons,
but you have people in there
who are guilty of nothing more
than showing up for work.
They're enabling
parasites.
Nobody gets a free pass.
Why aren't
the others moving, Noah?
Ahh. Inhalational anaesthetic.
They'll be out long enough.
Long enough for...? What are
you trying to achieve tonight?
You know, justice,
saving the world,
that kind of thing.
Big ask.
You don't strike me as the naive
type, Noah. Blake, maybe.
See, you have to see
the long game here, Claire.
You didn't listen to the Gretas.
You wouldn't listen
to the Marcus's.
You lose your shit if someone
throws oil at a painting,
blocks the motorway,
crashes the big match.
Well, too late, because
now you get someone like me.
I'm struggling to join the dots
between strapping
explosives to innocent people
and saving the world.
See, your first mistake
is thinking that anyone
in here is innocent.
Do you hate people, Noah?
I hate what we've
done to the world, yeah.
I mean, you're talking
about saving, what, 100 people?
These bastards have been raping
the planet and getting fat on it
and you still
think I'm the bad guy.
So this is
a numbers game for you.
There we go.
Speaking of numbers, Claire,
why are there five SWAT guys
sniffing around the entrance?
Get them back now.
- Pull back. Pull back!
- We're moving back, Noah.
Great, cos you have
five seconds, one per guy.
We're moving back.
And three, two...
I told you, we're back.
Well done, Claire. Thank you.
- Still there?
- They have families, Noah.
Well, now they don't. Like
you said, it's a numbers game.
What kind of numbers
depend on you, so till I'm done,
stay the fuck back.
Don't you
ever go behind my back again!
Five police officers
have been killed in a blast
at the Agnian Tower siege
in what is becoming a truly
horrific night for London.
The men were all
serving SCO19 officers.
Anti-humanist terrorist,
Noah Santos,
has yet to make any demands,
and so far no
hostages have been released.
- Joey.
- I warned you.
What the hell are you thinking?
Noah's hooked up
to a dead man's switch,
so we can't move our teams in,
we can't get the hostages out.
He's got us by the balls.
You, maybe. I'm going in.
- How are you gonna do that?
- I'm working on it.
Is there anything
else you can tell me?
We know that
Noah's after confessions
and Agnian files before
he goes live with it all,
and we think he's running
it through the control room.
I'll do my best.
You wanna hang this
whole operation
on a window cleaner
who couldn't hack the army?
At least she didn't just send
five men to their deaths, Royce.
We need an opening
and she can give us one.
Helping the pigs, that's
a new low, even for you, Joey.
Oh, I don't know. Beats murder.
I'm sorry that you stayed late,
I'm sorry that you got
in my way,
and I'm sorry that you can't
see what I'm trying to do here,
but that's irrelevant,
because by the end of tonight,
everyone will see,
and you're not stopping them.
Repeat,
I have visuals on an IED.
Joey, you need to move now.
Explosives coming your way.
Come on, Joey. Come on.
I knew that
the Agnian brand was associated
with pollution and exploitation.
I knew the Miltons'
reputation...
and I knowingly helped
to rebrand and greenwash
Agnian's criminal...
She's dead.
We have visual confirmation.
Joanna Locke is dead.
Messy. Bye-bye, bitch.
If you believe that.
Come on, Joey.
Tell me you're still there.
Yeah. Yeah, I'm here.
Thank God for that.
Are you okay?
I'm okay.
Stay dead.
It'll buy us some time.
Right.
Hopefully they won't see me
climbing in through that hole.
What hole?
The one your snipers are
gonna put through the glass.
On it.
As the personal assistant
to the Milton brothers,
I've been a silent
witness to a web of corruption.
Splitting the team's a risk.
So is assuming she's dead.
I need an update, Zee.
By the time you get Gerald's
confession, I'll be done.
Go.
I've allowed
myself to be manipulated...
You're up, Gerry.
What do you care what we say?
Do you really think anybody will
listen after what you've done?
Without the truth, no.
With the truth, enough will.
We're making
history tonight, Gerry.
And you'll let us go?
You have my word that we're
all going out the same way.
We've just received
this statement
from the Mayor of London
denouncing Noah Santos.
She says: 'I condemn this
senseless violence
and murder in the
strongest terms.'
'There can be no
justification whatsoever
for these
barbaric acts.'
'This is not activism.
It is terrorism.'
So, I know you
need to concentrate...
Don't stop.
Takes my mind off the
massive fall
and the dickheads with guns.
Climbing's the easy bit.
Been doing it since I was six.
How's the team with me going in?
Bet they loved me
bailing on the army.
Well, not to stress
you out or anything...
- You wanna know why I quit?
- You served four years.
You made it all the way through
selection only to walk away.
I grew up watching an
angry man act out
on everyone else
and I did nothing about it.
Get to the commando course,
one of the pricks I beat
couldn't handle being
beaten by a woman.
Huh.
He baited me, I bit.
Quit before they could bin me.
Could have fought your corner.
No, you don't do that.
Except this time.
This time it's
not just my corner.
Michael.
Whenever our dad
started on Michael,
I'd open the window, climb out,
sit on the ledge
till it was over.
This time I'm not leaving him.
I can be stubborn when I want.
Me too. Stubborn's
just what we need right now.
How does being stubborn
and hostage negotiation work?
Well, better
at work than at home.
You're a train wreck too?
Well, what do you want first?
Marriage one, two, three?
Right, listen, they're gonna be
onto you soon,
so let me call Noah.
If he's talking to me, then
he's not thinking about you.
That's cool.
Train wreck crew.
I wish to confess
to the profound misdeeds...
...that I
and my brother Geoffrey
presided over as CEOs of Agnian.
- Miss me, Claire?
- Well, I've been thinking.
You know what you
remind me of, Noah?
One of those wasps. I don't know
their name. You probably do.
They lay their eggs
in moth larvae
and then they take
over from within.
- Ichneumon wasps?
- Ichneumon wasps.
Marcus Blake, he was the moth.
You killed
everything Earth Revolution was.
You perverted everything
that Blake was fighting for.
You called me
just to tell me that?
Those hostages,
they must be close to waking up.
I think it's time we agreed
the best way they can walk out.
In 40 minutes,
we'll walk out with them
onto the coaches that
you are going
to allow through
the perimeter.
At which point,
we will drive 300 metres,
up St. Thomas Street,
where, provided you behave,
we'll release half the hostages.
Then?
Let's not get ahead
of ourselves, now.
I need assurances
you'll release all of them.
We will, once we're well clear
of here and the truth is out.
Any attempts
to get clever will result
in more bad headlines
and dead bodies.
In the following cases,
such as that of Elena Lanza,
contract killings were tacitly
but knowingly encouraged.
We are guilty.
And that's a fucking wrap.
Joey, we're running out of time.
Oh, my God.
- Are you okay?
- No, not okay.
I'm quite stressed.
Squeeze.
- Can I get up first?
- Yes. Good idea.
There's some
crazy stuff going on.
Hume, I'm in. I'm inside.
Well done. Now get moving.
They'll be coming for you.
- She's alive. She's inside.
- Then fucking find her.
- Come on, come on. Come on.
- What about the hostages?
- We're not gonna let them die.
- What about us?
- We're not gonna die either.
- What if we do?
Michael.
Michael, we have to go.
- I'm scared, Joanna.
- I'm scared too.
But we can't stop,
not here, not now.
Michael. Michael.
- I need you.
- You need me?
Noah's after some files.
I need you to hack them.
Remember when the Avengers
steal the Infinity Stones?
Yes, they had
to build a time machine.
Forget the time machine.
They steal the stones.
Thanos goes crazy trying
to get them back.
We're gonna steal
Noah's Infinity Stones.
- Just checking. You mean...
- The files.
I mean the files.
Okay, come on.
I told you what would happen
if you tried to interfere,
didn't I, Claire?
My teams haven't moved, Noah,
so if there's trouble on
the inside,
then it's outside
both our control.
You know ichneumon wasps,
they have another name.
They're a, they're
called Darwin wasps.
See, Darwin thought
that a creature surviving
through the
destruction of another
was proof against
the existence of God,
as if man wasn't proof enough.
But soon I'll have
the truth and so will you.
Bye Claire.
Did he just blink?
Man has no
preordained right to exist.
In fact, I'd argue that
we had our chance to exist
in balance with nature
and everything around us
and we set it all on fire.
No, I don't think he did.
He's gonna kill them all.
Quick.
If we get out of this,
can we do something together,
like a, like a joust?
Well, no, not a joust.
I can't ride a horse.
We could go snorkelling.
I don't like it here.
Yeah. Neither will they.
Stay here.
Put it down.
Joey!
So well, what now, great leader?
We show the world why we came.
Only one more confession
coming after Gerald's.
I need four minutes to encrypt,
then it's showtime.
Socials, news. There
won't be a feed it doesn't hit.
I hope it's worth it,
because so far the entire world
thinks you're a terrorist
whack job.
You'll see.
They'll all see.
My name is Noah Santos,
and by the time you see this,
myself and everyone in
this building will be dead.
What?
You'll have seen
the truth by now.
Agnian are guilty, like the
countless other
corporations that
plunder our planet.
I give you this truth
because you need to know
when they're counting the bodies
that my cause was just.
Man is a plague upon the Earth,
a virus.
- What the fuck is this?
- There is no more destructive,
rapacious filth...
I told you, true believers only.
Yeah, I truly believe
you're a fucking psycho.
Come on.
...the
building will be dead.
You'll have seen
the truth now...
Don't look at them.
Just do your thing. Michael.
...As is
everyone who enables them.
Insanity,
true insanity in this context,
would be watching the Earth
die beneath our very feet
while we do nothing about it.
I don't understand.
It's the truth.
For the earth to heal, the human
virus must be controlled.
I know it is,
but what about that?
Because there is no new dawn,
not with man in it.
Our extinction is inevitable,
deserved and necessary.
Yes, okay, that's bad.
We mustn't fear this.
So now we punish.
This is war, and there
will be no mercy, no quarter.
All flesh is just grass,
and with the harvest reaped,
the earth can renew.
- Come on, come on.
- Joanna, please, don't rush me.
...each and every one
of my brothers and sisters
to take up my crusade.
Let the blood
of the guilty spill,
light the fires around
them and burn it all down.
I need an update, Zee.
The update is
your plan's fucked.
I've got the evidence and your
weird angry-man YouTube rant.
It doesn't matter how
many people you kill, Noah,
no one will ever know why.
You're just another
psycho the world will hate.
- You're such a badass.
- So are you. Come on.
Hume, he's going
to blow the building.
He's going to kill everyone.
We know. We're coming in
- and you need to get out now.
- No.
I've got what he wants.
He'll come after me.
I'll deal with that switch.
You get as many people
out as you can.
The control room is empty.
They won't see you coming.
I'm sending my brother
down in the service lift.
- Get him clear of here.
- Copy that.
Hume, listen.
I need you to take care of him.
It's a numbers game, right?
Copy that, Joey. I will.
Good luck.
They're going to look after you.
You're going to be okay,
I promise.
- But you have to go.
- No, wait. What about you?
As long as Noah's chasing me,
they can save more people...
- No.
- and you can get out.
- No, but you need me.
- I'll be right behind you.
- I need you.
- You don't.
You were right, I was
never there for you. I wasn't.
- No, please.
- I wasn't, and I'm sorry.
- No.
- You were right.
- It was always later.
This time I'm not
gonna let you down.
Michael, please.
Please.
Bastard! You
said you'd let us go!
I said we were all
going out the same way.
- Where are you, Joey?
- Utility.
See if you can do
better than the last
three arseholes
you sent.
We get
one chance. We get in there,
get as many hostages
as you can and get out.
Do not kill Noah Santos. Repeat:
Do not kill Noah Santos.
If his pulse stops, it's over.
Everyone stay calm and still.
Ma'am,
we don't have time
to disarm this many devices,
not this complex.
If even one of them detonates,
it's gonna bring
down the whole building.
Hey, Joey.
I really wish you
could see what I see.
A world with nobody.
It's beautiful.
Do you still
wanna end me? Go ahead.
Look. I'll make it easy for you.
Come on, do it.
Do it. Do it,
Joey. Just fucking do it!
Nice, Joey.
Finally putting other people's
interests above your own.
Shame, though, it's the wrong
people. Now give me the drive.
Do you think I'd be dumb enough
to keep it on me? Fuck you!
- Where the fuck is it?
- It's gone.
No one will ever
know why you did this.
I guess they'll just
have to figure it out, then.
No!
Ready.
All flesh is grass.
I guess you lose.
Yeah.
No.
Later, Noah
Joey.
Train wreck crew.
- Michael?
- Safe.
- You did a good job up there.
- Beats cleaning windows.
Right, there'll be more
debriefs. Go get some rest.
Debriefs can come later.
And the evidence that you took.
The higher-ups are
insisting you hand it over,
just so that this
can all get processed
through the correct channels.
It would be
a shame if after all that,
all those dirty little secrets
stayed buried, wouldn't it?
Yeah, it would.
Hmm.
We don't have it. We never did.
I was bluffing
to make Noah bite.
That's what I thought. Smart.
You did a good
thing tonight, Joey.
Don't stop now.
- The 33 million...
- That you have to give back.
Do you need a squeeze?
Got the drive?
I have the drive.
They're calling
it the "Earth Revolution leaks".
Following the death of
anti-humanist
terrorist Noah Santos,
the anonymous
leaks have lifted the lid
on a tsunami of corruption
at the highest levels
of the energy industry.
One question remains:
will the ripples of this scandal
change the course
of the climate crisis,
or will it be business as usual?
This is nice.
Really nice.
Do you
think they'll go to jail?
I hope so.
- I think they will.
- Maybe.
Piers Morgan,
eat your heart out.
Yeah.
- You okay?
- I'm better than okay.
- It's just...
- What?
Something's
been bugging me since the tower.
Okay.
Okay, Thanos didn't
just hunt down
the Avengers' Infinity Stones.
I don't think that's
doing the Russo brothers,
Kevin Feige or Endgame justice.
That's been bugging you?
Look, I just
feel like you simplified it.
Mmm...
We were in an armed siege.
Okay...